[{"answer": "I don't know you at all", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Who is this", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I'm not the degenerate.  You are, my friend", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Infinitely more than you know about me", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Who the hell is this", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "my friend?  Is that true?  Are you there", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You know that", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What man", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "And what did this guy say", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Making calls is part of my business", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "You're not going to start that shit again", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "What could be wrong", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What could be wrong", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Yeah?  Who do I sound like", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I told you.  In a while", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Why should he call back", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Suppose that's the only way I can get to you?  You claim you love her", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You don't even love yourself", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What do you do, exactly", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What've you kept out", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You weren't particularly convincing", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Because you don't really believe my Remington is pointed at you", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I didn't really believe in what I was saying", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I do", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "If I flick this, I use it", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Make me an offer", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Come on, man.  That's my good watch", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Then here.  Take the damn thing", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Maybe if the city provided decent public toilets, folks wouldn't relieve themselves in the subway stations and phone booths", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Next thing you know you're gonna claim we mugged you", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Yeah.  Sucking chest wound right over the heart", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Call the meatwagon.  He's fucked up", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I gave him my money, my watch..", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "He was a fucking thief", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "None of your business", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I've got no side of it", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "A cellular?  Then what are you doing in a phone booth making calls", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Don't reach for it, mister", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "It'll be hard to find a lawyer willing to risk his life.  But if you hand over the gun..", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "We'll take it out for you", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "We're not about to force you because there could be a miscalculation and then we'd never find out why this happened", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "It's what makes the job interesting.  Finding out why. Something drove you to do this. You didn't go out today expecting this to happen.  It was a nice day. You were out for a walk.  And then suddenly it all changed", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "I'd never get the words out.  Not with fifteen or twenty rounds in me", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "They wouldn't wait to see", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Slide your finger up under the plastic and you'll feel the cold metal surface.  There are four rounds left in it.  Should you decide to shoot your way out", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "You could shoot me, my friend.  You'd do that in a minute if you could", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "I want to see that you exist.  Like God exists.  It's not enough to believe.  You want to see him", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Show yourself to me and I'll take the gun down.  I swear", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "There won't be much point in harming them without you around to impress", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Let me see you do it", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "It's okay.  I'm not really shot", "docId": "Phone-Booth.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "I thought so, too.  But we're going to be alright.  Both of us", "qsentId": 52}]